Dhyan Patel

Scarborough, ON M1S3E6 dhyanapatel2003@gmail.com +1 437 985 7923

Achieving a good job responsibility that compels me to use my personal skills to the highest levels so that it can benefit the firm I am working for and add to my work experience. Learn something new everyday and use it to improve my work ethics as well as for my own betterment.

Work Experience

Food Counter Attendant

Demetres - Danforth Station, ON June 2022 to Present

- 1. Made orders on time and working on the counter.
- 2. Working as a dishwasher.
- 3. Maintaining the inventory.

(Scarborough)

241 Pizza Store (Manager) February 2022 to May 2022

- 1. Taking orders from the customer at the screen and interacting with them.
- 2. Timely making pizzas, pasta, wings and much more according to the order.
- 3. Handled customer complaints.
- 4. Managed the accounts of the store.

Desk job (Ahmedabad

Excel Immigration India)

January 2021 to December 2021

https://excelimmigration.business.site/?utm_source=gmb&utm_medium=referral

- 1. Handled clients' calls, emails, and social media.
- 2. Customer Greeting, interaction, and support.
- 3. Reviewing ongoing cases and sharing its update to clients.

Club House Manager

(Swikar Tenaments Society)

December 2019 to December 2020

- 1. Managed all the equipments of the gym, sports materials and was in charge of supervising the cleaning of the club house.
- 2. Handled society members' complains regarding anything.
- 3. Managed all the accounts of the club house and reported to the secretary.

Badminton Coach

Sun and step sports academy - Ahmedabad, Gujarat May 2016 to March 2020 I was an assistant coach at this academy and trained many students under me. I used to design workout requirements and diet requirements for them too. Made them practice all the drills and footwork required on the court

Education

Advanced diploma in Computer Programming

Seneca college - Toronto, ON January 2022 to Present

Skills

- Enthusiast
- Leadership and Managing people
- Well disciplined
- Microsoft Office Proficient
- Computer Proficient
- Retail Management
- Recruiting
- Store Management Experience
- Account Management
- Sales Management
- Merchandising
- Interviewing
- Account Management
- · Interviewing
- Retail Sales
- Cash Handling
- Assistant Manager Experience
- Pricing
- Research
- Purchasing
- Quality Assurance
- Sales

Languages

- English Fluent
- Hindi Fluent
- Gujarati Fluent

Links

https://www.linkedin.com/in/dhyanp

Awards

State Tournament

May 2017

I was ranked in top 10 singles player of Gujarat state in India